BRITT RAE JACK

Moriarty, NM 87035 ● (505) 252-8571 ● brittanyjack1989@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/britt-rae-jack • github.com/BrittRJack

Professional Summary

Driven professional with experience in project design and management.

Completed multiple independent projects including personal websites and database design. Interested in a career as a junior-level Web Developer.

Skills

- Data mapping
- Creative design
- HTML and CSS
- Data collection and analysis

- Fluent in Spanish
- SQL and databases
- Online marketing strategies
- JavaScript, PHP and, Angular

Work History

Student Internship, 10/2018 to Current

CNM Deep Dive Coding Bootcamp - Albuquerque, NM

- Contributed to the development of a capstone project
- Developed wireframes, site maps and content in databases
- Developed object-oriented software in PHP
- Coded 3 websites using JavaScript, CSS, HTML
- Met with project managers on a weekly basis to provide a detailed project report and milestone updates
- Implemented Git for version control
- Wrote clean, clear and well-tested code for various projects

Youth Program Manager, 12/2013 to 09/2018

Norwegian Cruise Line Holdings Ltd.- 5 Years - Miami, FL

- Trained and integrated new staff into the company's policies and procedures
- Conducted interviews for potential employees
- Was responsible for the safety and care of 1,100 children weekly
- Followed up with guests' concerns
- Kept detailed records and data from every voyage

English Language Teacher, 03/2009 to 12/2013

YMCA Inc - 4 Years - Augusta, MI

- Designed exams to test fluency in reading, writing, speaking and comprehension of the English language.
- Planned lessons for classroom of 30 students.
- Corresponded with students and parents through email, telephone or postal mail.
- Voted teacher of the year by the University of Santo Tomas, Colombia

Education

Certificate Of Completion: Full-Stack Software Development, 2018

Central New Mexico Stemulus - Albuquerque, NM